Guide to the National Lawyers Guild Records TAM.191
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Part 2, Series VIII: NLG v. AG - Discovery, 1921-1987
  - Subseries H: Released Government Documents, FBI Field Offices.
    - Mexico City: Crockett, George W., 1962-1963, Undated (Box 215, Folder 15)
    - Mexico City: Kinoy, Arthur, Undated (Box 215, Folder 16)
    - Mexico City: Margolis, Benjamin, Undated (Box 215, Folder 17)
    - Mexico City: Rabinowitz, Victor, 1963-1976, Undated (Box 215, Folder 18)
    - Mexico City: Rein, David, Undated (Box 215, Folder 19)
    - Mexico City: Smith, William, 1971-1976, Undated (Box 215, Folder 20)
    - Mexico City: Stender, Fay, Undated (Box 215, Folder 21)
    - Miami, 1950-1957 (Box 215, Folder 22)
    - Miami, 1955-1974 (Box 215, Folder 23)
    - Miami, 1962-1974 (Box 215, Folder 24)
    - Milwaukee, 1946-1975 (Box 215, Folder 25)
    - Milwaukee, 1950-1977 (Box 215, Folder 26)
    - Minneapolis, 1948-1976 (Box 215, Folder 27)
    - Minneapolis, 1948-1977 (Box 215, Folder 28)
    - Minneapolis, 1950-1974 (Box 215, Folder 29)
    - Mobile, 1955-1974 (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - New Haven, 1949-1970 (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - New Haven: Part 1, 1947-1950 (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - New Haven: Part 1 [I], 1947-1972 (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - New Haven: Part 1 [II], 1947-1972 (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - New Haven: Part 2 [I], 1950-1954 (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - New Haven: Part 2 [II], 1950-1954 (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - New Haven: Part 3 [I], 1954-1959 (Box 216, Folder 8)
    - New Haven: Part 3 [II], 1954-1959 (Box 216, Folder 9)
    - New Haven: Part 4 [I], 1943-1963 (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - New Haven: Part 4 [II], 1943-1963 (Box 216, Folder 11)
    - New Haven: Part 4, 1959-1968 (Box 216, Folder 12)
    - New Haven: Part 5 [I], 1952-1975 (Box 216, Folder 13)
    - New Haven: Part 5 [II], 1952-1975 (Box 216, Folder 14)
    - New Haven: Part 5, 1970-1975 (Box 216, Folder 15)
    - New Haven: Section 3, 1950-1974 (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - New Orleans [I], 1948-1977 (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - New Orleans [II], 1948-1977 (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - New Orleans, 1950-1974 (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - New Orleans, 1953-1955 (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - New York: Section 1, 1942-1951 (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - New York: Section 2-I [I], 1951-1953 (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - New York: Section 2-I [II], 1951-1953 (Box 217, Folder 8)
    - New York: Section 2-II [I], 1951-1953 (Box 217, Folder 9)
    - New York: Section 2-II [II], 1951-1953 (Box 217, Folder 10)
    - New York: Section 3, 1950-1953 (Box 217, Folder 11)
    - New York: Section 4-I [I], 1950-1954 (Box 217, Folder 12)
    - New York: Section 4-I [II], 1950-1954 (Box 217, Folder 13)
    - New York: Section 4-II [I], 1950-1954 (Box 217, Folder 14)
    - New York: Section 4-II [II], 1950-1954 (Box 217, Folder 15)
    - New York: Section 5-I [I], 1954-1955 (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - New York: Section 5-I [II], 1954-1955 (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - New York: Section 5-II, 1950-1954 (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - New York: Section 6-I [I], 1955-1957 (Box 218, Folder 4)
    - New York: Section 6-I [II], 1955-1957 (Box 218, Folder 5)
    - New York: Section 6-II [I], 1950-1958 (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - New York: Section 6-II [II], 1950-1958 (Box 218, Folder 7)
    - New York: Section 6-III, 1947-1965 (Box 218, Folder 8)
    - New York: Section 7-I, 1957-1958 (Box 218, Folder 9)
    - New York: Section 7-II, 1957-1958 (Box 218, Folder 10)
    - New York: Section 8-I, 1958-1959 (Box 218, Folder 11)
    - New York: Section 8-II, 1958-1959 (Box 218, Folder 12)
    - New York: Section 9-I, 1959-1960 (Box 218, Folder 13)
    - New York: Section 9-II, 1959-1960 (Box 218, Folder 14)
    - New York: Section 10-I, 1960-1961 (Box 218, Folder 15)
    - New York: Section 10-II, 1960-1961 (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - New York: Section 11-I, 1961-1962 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - New York: Section 11-I, 1961-1962 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - New York: Section 12-I, 1958-1964 (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - New York: Section 12-II, 1958-1964 (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - New York: Section 13-I, 1964-1966 (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - New York: Section 13-II, 1964-1965 (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - New York: Section 14-I, 1966-1968 (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - New York: Section 14-II, 1966-1968 (Box 219, Folder 9)
    - New York: Section 15-I [I], 1968-1973 (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - New York: Section 15-I [II], 1969-1973 (Box 219, Folder 11)
    - New York: Section 15-II [I], 1968-1973 (Box 219, Folder 12)
    - New York: Section 15-II [II], 1968-1973 (Box 219, Folder 13)
    - New York: Section 16-I, 1971-1973 (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - New York: Section 16-II, 1971-1973 (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - New York: Section 17-I, 1973-1974 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - New York: Section 17-II, 1972-1974 (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - New York: Section 18-I [I], 1973-1976 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - New York: Section 18-I [II], 1973-1976 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - New York: Section 18-II, 1974-1976 (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - New York: Section 19-I, 1952-1954 (Box 220, Folder 8)
    - New York: Section 19-II, 1953-1954 (Box 220, Folder 9)
    - New York: List of 1B Enclosures - I, 1947-1974 (Box 220, Folder 10)
    - New York: List of 1B Enclosures - II, 1947-1974 (Box 220, Folder 11)
    - New York: 1B Enclosures - 1, 1938-1953 (Box 220, Folder 12)
    - New York: 1B Enclosures - 2 [I], 1941-1954 (Box 220, Folder 13)
    - New York: 1B Enclosures - 2 [II], 1941-1954 (Box 220, Folder 14)
    - New York: 1B Enclosures - 3, 1937-1962 (Box 220, Folder 15)
    - New York: 1B Enclosures - 3 and 4, Undated (Box 220, Folder 16)
    - New York: 1B Enclosures - 4 [I], 1938-1946 (Box 220, Folder 17)
    - New York: 1B Enclosures - 4 [II], 1938-1946 (Box 220, Folder 18)
    - New York: 1B Enclosures - 5 [I], 1948-1960 (Box 220, Folder 19)
    - New York: 1B Enclosures - 5 [II], 1948-1960 (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - New York: 1B Enclosures - 6 [I], 1947-1965 (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - New York: 1B Enclosures - 6 [II], 1947-1965 (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - New York: 1B Enclosures - 7.1, 1965-1973 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - New York: 1B Enclosures - 7.2 [I], 1965-1978 (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - New York: 1B Enclosures - 7.2 [II], 1965-1978 (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - New York: See References - Part 1, 1944-1983 (Box 221, Folder 7)
    - New York: See References - Part 2, 1943-1983 (Box 221, Folder 8)
    - New York: See References - Part 3, 1939-1968 (Box 221, Folder 9)
    - New York: See References - Part 4, 1969-1984 (Box 221, Folder 10)
    - Newark, 1948-1972 (Box 221, Folder 11)
    - Newark, 1949-1974 (Box 221, Folder 12)
    - Norfolk, 1948-1972 (Box 221, Folder 13)
    - Norfolk, 1948-1974 (Box 221, Folder 14)
    - Norfolk: 100-4626, 1948-1974 (Box 221, Folder 15)
    - Oklahoma City, 1972-1973 (Box 221, Folder 16)
    - Oklahoma City, 1972-1975 (Box 221, Folder 17)
    - Omaha, 1948-1964 (Box 221, Folder 18)
    - Omaha, 1950-1975 (Box 221, Folder 19)
    - Omaha, 1955-1975 (Box 221, Folder 20)
    - Philadelphia, 1941-1975 (Box 221, Folder 21)
    - Philadelphia: Volume 1 [I], 1946-1970 (Box 221, Folder 22)
    - Philadelphia: Volume 1 [II], 1946-1970 (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - Philadelphia: Volume 2, 1946-1976 (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - Philadelphia [I], 1946-1976 (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Philadelphia [II], 1946-1976 (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - Philadelphia [III], 1946-1976 (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - Philadelphia [IV], 1946-1976 (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - Philadelphia [I], 1948-1959 (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - Philadelphia [II], 1948-1959 (Box 222, Folder 8)
    - Phoenix, 1948 (Box 222, Folder 9)
    - Phoenix, 1950-1974 (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - Phoenix, 1950-1975 (Box 222, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh, 1941-1974 (Box 222, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh, 1952-1972 (Box 222, Folder 13)
    - Portland: Copy 1 [I], 1938-1975 (Box 222, Folder 14)
    - Portland: Copy 1 [II], 1938-1975 (Box 222, Folder 15)
    - Portland: Copy 2 [I], 1938-1975 (Box 222, Folder 16)
    - Portland: Copy 2 [II], 1938-1975 (Box 222, Folder 17)
    - Portland, 1972 (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Richmond, 1941-1975 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - Richmond, 1948-1974 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - Richmond, 1953 (Box 223, Folder 4)
    - Sacramento, 1971-1976 (Box 223, Folder 5)
    - Sacramento, 1972-1975 (Box 223, Folder 6)
    - St. Louis, 1947-1975 (Box 223, Folder 7)
    - St. Louis, 1953-1976 (Box 223, Folder 8)
    - San Antonio [I], 1948-1976 (Box 223, Folder 9)
    - San Antonio [II], 1948-1976 (Box 223, Folder 10)
    - San Antonio: Copy I [I], 1955-1976 (Box 223, Folder 11)
    - San Antonio: Copy I [II], 1955-1976 (Box 223, Folder 12)
    - San Antonio: Copy II [I], 1955-1976 (Box 223, Folder 13)
    - San Antonio: Copy II [II], 1955-1976 (Box 223, Folder 14)
    - San Antonio, 1973, Undated (Box 223, Folder 15)
    - San Diego, 1948-1975 (Box 223, Folder 16)
    - San Diego [I], 1951-1975 (Box 223, Folder 17)
    - San Diego [II], 1951-1975 (Box 223, Folder 18)
    - San Francisco: Section 1-I, 1966-1967 (Box 223, Folder 19)
    - San Francisco: Section 1-II, 1966-1967 (Box 223, Folder 20)
    - San Francisco: Section 2-I, 1964-1965 (Box 223, Folder 21)
    - San Francisco: Section 2-II, 1964-1966 (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco: Section 3 and 4-I, 1964-1965 (Box 224, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco: Section 3 and 4-II, 1964-1965 (Box 224, Folder 3)
    - San Francisco: Section 5-I, 1963-1964 (Box 224, Folder 4)
    - San Francisco: Section 5-II, 1963-1964 (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco: Section 6-I, 1962-1963 (Box 224, Folder 6)
    - San Francisco: Section 6-II, 1962-1963 (Box 224, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco: Section 7, 11 and 16-I, 1954-1962 (Box 224, Folder 8)
    - San Francisco: Section 7, 11 and 16-II, 1954-1962 (Box 224, Folder 9)
    - San Francisco: Section 8-I, 1961-1962 (Box 224, Folder 10)
    - San Francisco: Section 8-II, 1961-1962 (Box 224, Folder 11)
    - San Francisco: Section 9-I, 1960-1961 (Box 224, Folder 12)
    - San Francisco: Section 9-II, 1960-1961 (Box 224, Folder 13)
    - San Francisco: Section 10-I, 1960 (Box 224, Folder 14)
    - San Francisco: Section 10-II, 1960 (Box 224, Folder 15)
    - San Francisco: Section 12-I, 1958-1959 (Box 224, Folder 16)
    - San Francisco: Section 12-II, 1958-1959 (Box 224, Folder 17)
    - San Francisco: Section 13-I, 1956-1958 (Box 224, Folder 18)
    - San Francisco: Section 13-II, 1956-1958 (Box 224, Folder 19)
    - San Francisco: Section 14-I, 1956 (Box 224, Folder 20)
    - San Francisco: Section 14-II, 1956 (Box 224, Folder 21)
    - San Francisco: Section 15-I, 1955-1956 (Box 224, Folder 22)
    - San Francisco: Section 15-II, 1955-1956 (Box 224, Folder 23)
    - San Francisco: Section 17-I, 1952-1953 (Box 224, Folder 24)
    - San Francisco: Section 17-II, 1952-1953 (Box 224, Folder 25)
    - San Francisco: Section 18-I, 1951-1952 (Box 224, Folder 26)
    - San Francisco: Section 18-II, 1951-1952 (Box 224, Folder 27)
    - San Francisco: Section 19-I, 1950-1951 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco: Section 19-II, 1950-1951 (Box 225, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco: Section 20-I, 1950 (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - San Francisco: Section 20-II, 1950 (Box 225, Folder 4)
    - San Francisco: Section 21-I, 1950 (Box 225, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco: Section 21-II, 1950 (Box 225, Folder 6)
    - San Francisco: Section 22-I, 1950 (Box 225, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco: Section 22-II, 1950 (Box 225, Folder 8)
    - San Francisco: Section 23-I, 1942-1950 (Box 225, Folder 9)
    - San Francisco: Section 23-II, 1942-1950 (Box 225, Folder 10)
    - San Francisco: Section 24, 25 and 26-I, 1940-1971 (Box 225, Folder 11)
    - San Francisco: Section 24, 25 and 26-II, 1940-1971 (Box 225, Folder 12)
    - San Francisco: Section 27-I, 1944-1975 (Box 225, Folder 13)
    - San Francisco: Section 27-II, 1944-1975 (Box 225, Folder 14)
    - San Francisco: Section 28-I, 1953-1976 (Box 225, Folder 15)
    - San Francisco: Section 28-II, 1953-1976 (Box 225, Folder 16)
    - San Francisco: Section 29-I, 1975 (Box 225, Folder 17)
    - San Francisco: Section 29-II, 1975 (Box 225, Folder 18)
    - San Francisco: Section 30-I, 1974-1975 (Box 225, Folder 19)
    - San Francisco: Section 30-II, 1974-1975 (Box 225, Folder 20)
    - San Francisco: Section 31-I, 1974 (Box 225, Folder 21)
    - San Francisco: Section 31-II, 1974 (Box 225, Folder 22)
    - San Francisco: Section 32-I, 1973 (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco: Section 32-II, 1973 (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco: Section 33-I, 1973 (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - San Francisco: Section 33-II, 1973 (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - San Francisco: Section 34-I, 1971-1973 (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco: Section 34-II, 1972-1973 (Box 226, Folder 6)
    - San Francisco: Section 35-I, 1972 (Box 226, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco: Section 35-II, 1972 (Box 226, Folder 8)
    - San Francisco: Section 36-I, 1971-1972 (Box 226, Folder 9)
    - San Francisco: Section 36-II, 1971-1972 (Box 226, Folder 10)
    - San Francisco: Section 37-I, 1971 (Box 226, Folder 11)
    - San Francisco: Section 37-II, 1971 (Box 226, Folder 12)
    - San Francisco: Section 38-I, 1970-1971 (Box 226, Folder 13)
    - San Francisco: Section 38-II, 1970-1971 (Box 226, Folder 14)
    - San Francisco: Section 39-I, 1969-1970 (Box 226, Folder 15)
    - San Francisco: Section 39-II, 1969-1970 (Box 226, Folder 16)
    - San Francisco: Section 40-I, 1968-1970 (Box 226, Folder 17)
    - San Francisco: Section 40-II, 1968-1970 (Box 226, Folder 18)
    - San Francisco: Section 41-I, 1968-1969 (Box 226, Folder 19)
    - San Francisco: Section 41-II, 1968-1969 (Box 226, Folder 20)
    - San Francisco: Section 42-I, 1967-1968 (Box 226, Folder 21)
    - San Francisco: Section 42-II, 1967-1968 (Box 226, Folder 22)
    - San Francisco: Section 43-I, 1966-1968 (Box 226, Folder 23)
    - San Francisco: Section 43-II, 1966-1968 (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco: Section 44, 1964-1968 (Box 227, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco: Section 45-I, 1942-1971 (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - San Francisco: Section 45-II, 1943-1953 (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - San Francisco: Section 46, 1957-1962 (Box 227, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco: Section 47 and 57, 1943-1958 (Box 227, Folder 6)
    - San Francisco: Section 48 and 63, 1972 (Box 227, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco: Section 49, 1964-1968 (Box 227, Folder 8)
    - San Francisco: Section 50, 1962-1964 (Box 227, Folder 9)
    - San Francisco: Section 51, 1969-1971 (Box 227, Folder 10)
    - San Francisco: Section 52, 1961-1962 (Box 227, Folder 11)
    - San Francisco: Section 53, 1959-1961 (Box 227, Folder 12)
    - San Francisco: Section 54, 1957-1958 (Box 227, Folder 13)
    - San Francisco: Section 55, 1954-1966 (Box 227, Folder 14)
    - San Francisco: Section 56, 1952 (Box 227, Folder 15)
    - San Francisco: Section 57, 1949-1950 (Box 227, Folder 16)
    - San Francisco: Section 58, 1962-1964 (Box 227, Folder 17)
    - San Francisco: Section 59, 1951-1953 (Box 227, Folder 18)
    - San Francisco: Section 60-I, 1943-1969 (Box 227, Folder 19)
    - San Francisco: Section 60-II, 1941-1973 (Box 227, Folder 20)
    - San Francisco: Section 61-I, 1951-1968 (Box 227, Folder 21)
    - San Francisco: Section 61-II, 1952 (Box 227, Folder 22)
    - San Francisco: Section 62-I, 1967 (Box 227, Folder 23)
    - San Francisco: Section 62-II, 1967 (Box 227, Folder 24)
    - San Francisco: Section 64, 1963 (Box 227, Folder 25)
    - San Francisco: Section 65, 1968-1976 (Box 227, Folder 26)
    - San Francisco: Section 66, 1953-1957 (Box 227, Folder 27)
    - San Francisco: Section 67 and 69, 1943-1977 (Box 227, Folder 28)
    - San Francisco: Section 68, 1950-1951 (Box 227, Folder 29)
    - San Francisco: Section 70-I, 1939-1956 (Box 227, Folder 30)
    - San Francisco: Section 70-II, 1938-1975 (Box 228, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco: Section 71, 1944-1945 (Box 228, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco: Section 72 [I], 1957-1966 (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - San Francisco: Section 72 [II], 1957-1966 (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - San Francisco: Enclosures [I], 1958-1970 (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco: Enclosures [II], 1958-1970 (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - San Francisco: Enclosures [III], 1958-1970 (Box 228, Folder 7)
    - Savannah, 1946-1974 (Box 228, Folder 8)
    - Seattle, 1949-1979 (Box 228, Folder 9)
    - Seattle, 1951-1973 (Box 228, Folder 10)
    - Springfield, 1953-1972 (Box 228, Folder 11)
    - Springfield [I], 1956-1974 (Box 228, Folder 12)
    - Springfield [II], 1956-1974 (Box 228, Folder 13)
    - Tampa, 1974 (Box 228, Folder 14)
    - Tokyo, 1957-1977 (Box 228, Folder 15)
    - Washington, 1941-1950 (Box 228, Folder 16)
    - Washington, 1941-1953 (Box 228, Folder 17)
    - Washington, 1941-1968 (Box 228, Folder 18)
    - Washington [I], 1941-1975 (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - Washington [II], 1941-1975 (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - Washington [III], 1941-1975 (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - Washington [IV], 1941-1975 (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - Washington [V], 1941-1975 (Box 229, Folder 5)
    - Washington [I], 1950-1976 (Box 229, Folder 6)
    - Washington [II], 1950-1976 (Box 229, Folder 7)
    - Washington, 1969-1976 (Box 229, Folder 8)
    - Washington, 1973-1974 (Box 229, Folder 9)
    - Washington, Undated (Box 229, Folder 10)
    - Various: Atlanta, Butte, New Orleans, Jacksonville, 1977-1987 (Box 229, Folder 11)
    - Various: Buffalo, Pittsburgh, Minneapolis, Charlotte, Baltimore, Washington, 1977-1987 (Box 229, Folder 12)
    - Various: Detroit, San Diego, Albuquerque, 1977-1987 (Box 229, Folder 13)
    - Various: Washington, San Francisco, Savannah, 1977-1987 (Box 229, Folder 14)
    - Various: [Houston], Undated (Box 229, Folder 15)
  - Subseries I: Released Government Documents, FBI Programs.
    - COINTELPRO: Part 1 of 4, HQ 100-3-104 and HQ 100-3-104 Sub 9 [I], 1958-1978 (Box 229, Folder 16)
    - COINTELPRO: Part 1 of 4, HQ 100-3-104 and HQ 100-3-104 Sub 9 [II], 1958-1978 (Box 229, Folder 17)
    - COINTELPRO: Part 2 of 4, HQ 100-3-104 and HQ 100-3-104 Sub 11, 15, 26, 34 and 47 [I], 1962-1967 (Box 229, Folder 18)
    - COINTELPRO: Part 2 of 4, HQ 100-3-104 and HQ 100-3-104 Subs 11, 15, 26, 34 and 47 [II], 1962-1967 (Box 229, Folder 19)
    - COINTELPRO: Part 3 of 4, HQ 100-448006; HQ 100-449698 and Subs 7, 9, 15 and 34, 1968-1971 (Box 229, Folder 20)
    - COINTELPRO: Part 4 of 4, HQ 62-88217-2476 [I], [1958] (Box 229, Folder 21)
    - COINTELPRO: Part 4 of 4, HQ 62-88217-2476 [II], [1958] (Box 229, Folder 22)
    - Department of Justice (DOJ) Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 19 [I], 1947-1958 (Box 229, Folder 23)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 19 [II], 1947-1958 (Box 229, Folder 24)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 20, Albany NLG Chapter, 1950-1953 (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 21, Baltimore NLG Chapter, 1947-1953 (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 22, Chicago NLG Chapter, 1953-1957 (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 23, Cleveland NLG Chapter, 1947-1954 (Box 230, Folder 4)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 24, Detroit NLG Chapter, 1951-1956 (Box 230, Folder 5)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 25, District of Columbia NLG Chapter, 1956 (Box 230, Folder 6)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 26, Los Angeles NLG Chapter, 1947-1956 (Box 230, Folder 7)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 27, New York City NLG Chapter, 1947-1956 (Box 230, Folder 8)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 28, Philadelphia NLG Chapter, 1949-1956 (Box 230, Folder 9)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 29, San Francisco NLG Chapter, 1953-1956 (Box 230, Folder 10)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 30, Boston NLG Chapter, 1950-1954 (Box 230, Folder 11)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 31, NLG At Large Members, Various States, 1950-1956 (Box 230, Folder 12)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 32, NLG Chapters, Various States, 1947-1956 (Box 230, Folder 13)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 33, NLG Chapters, Various States, 1947-1956 (Box 230, Folder 14)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 34, NLG Officers and Members, 1949 (Box 230, Folder 15)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 35, NLG Officers and Members, 1949 (Box 230, Folder 16)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 36, NLG Mailing List, 1953 (Box 230, Folder 17)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 41, Informants, 1956-1957 (Box 230, Folder 18)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 42, Informants, 1950-1957 (Box 230, Folder 19)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 43, Cleveland - Indiana, 1947-1957 (Box 230, Folder 20)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 44, Kansas - Oregon, 1947-1957 (Box 230, Folder 21)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 45, Phoenix - Wisconsin, 1949-1956 (Box 230, Folder 22)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 46, NLG Officers, National and Chapter, 1947-1956 (Box 230, Folder 23)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 47, Communist Party Ties to Officers, 1957 (Box 230, Folder 24)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 48, Communist Party Ties to Officers, 1957 (Box 231, Folder 1)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 49, Communist Party Ties to Officers, 1957 (Box 231, Folder 2)
    - DOJ Reports: Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 50, Communist Party Ties to Officers, 1957 (Box 231, Folder 3)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 1 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 19 [I], 1947-1958 (Box 231, Folder 4)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 1 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 19 [II], 1947-1958 (Box 231, Folder 5)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 1 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 20, 1950-1953 (Box 231, Folder 6)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 1 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 21, 1947-1953 (Box 231, Folder 7)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 2 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 22, 1953-1957 (Box 231, Folder 8)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 2 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 23, 1947-1954 (Box 231, Folder 9)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 2 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 24, 1951-1956 (Box 231, Folder 10)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 2 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 25, 1956 (Box 231, Folder 11)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 2 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 26, 1947-1956 (Box 231, Folder 12)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 2 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 27, 1947-1956 (Box 231, Folder 13)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 2 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 28, 1949-1956 (Box 231, Folder 14)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 3 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 29, 1953-1956 (Box 231, Folder 15)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 3 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 30, 1950-1954 (Box 231, Folder 16)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 3 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 31, 1950-1956 (Box 231, Folder 17)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 3 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 32, 1947-1956 (Box 231, Folder 18)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 3 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 33, 1947-1956 (Box 231, Folder 19)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 3 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 34, 1949 (Box 231, Folder 20)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 4 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 35, 1949 (Box 231, Folder 21)
    - DOJ Reports, Reprocessed (Part 4 of 7): Justice File 146-1-16-241, Serial 36, 1953 (Box 231, Folder 22)